fantasyguruelite.com 2018-12-30

# Privacy Policy | FantasyGuruElite

This web site, [www.fantasyguruelite.com](http://www.fantasyguruelite.com/) (the "Site"), is operated by Guru Fantasy Reports Inc. ("Guru Fantasy Reports Inc." or “we” or “our” or “us”). Your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use and disclose your personal information. It is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy carefully, especially before providing any personal information through the Site.

POLICY AGREEMENT

By accessing and using the Site, you agree to all of the policies, terms, and conditions on the Site, including the collection, use and disclosure of information as described herein. We encourage you to periodically review these policies as we may choose to change them occasionally to reflect industry initiatives, changes in the law or technology or changes in our practices regarding information collection, use and disclosure. If we make revisions to the way we collect, use or disclose personal information, we may provide notice of those changes by either: (1) announcing the change on the home page of the Site or (2) taking such other action as we deem appropriate under the circumstances, including without limitation, posting the revised draft of this Privacy Policy on the Site. You can determine when this Privacy Policy was last revised by referring to the “Last Updated” legend at the top of this page. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective upon posting of the revised Privacy Policy on the Internet, accessible through the Site. By continuing to use the Site following such changes, you will be deemed to have agreed to such changes. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, as it may be amended from time to time, in whole or in part, please do not continue using the Site.

GENERAL PRIVACY INFORMATION

The Site contains links to partners, advertisers and third party Internet sites and services that may collect data in connection with sweepstakes, promotions, e-commerce, etc. They each have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of the Site. Guru Fantasy Reports Inc. takes no responsibility for these independent policies or actions and cannot be held liable for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. Please be advised that any voluntary and public disclosure of personal information on any online service or Website - for example on message boards, through email or in chat areas – is information that can be collected and used by others. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Further, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online.

GENERAL RESTRICTIONS

Guru Fantasy Reports Inc. is the owner and/or licensee of all content displayed on the Site. Material from the Site may only be copied or printed for your own personal use in connection with your purchase of a service or product offered on the Site. None of the material appearing on the Site may be copied, distributed, modified, re-posted or otherwise displayed for public or commercial purposes without the written consent of Guru Fantasy Reports Inc. All of the trademarks, service marks, and other identifying marks used and displayed on the Site are owned by Guru Fantasy Reports Inc. or by others with whom Guru Fantasy Reports Inc. has an agreement/partnership. The Site is copyright protected.

COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

Guru Fantasy Reports Inc. collects various types of information from the guests and users of the Site. Customer contact information, collected during the account registration process, is used to send the user information about us and other promotional material. It is also used to contact the user when necessary for customer service reasons. Other information is collected specifically in order to improve the Site, to learn more about the user’s needs, to target advertising to users of the Site or to accomplish other business purposes. Guru Fantasy Reports Inc. reserves the right to use all information collected for any legally permissible purpose including, but not limited to, the emailing of advertising and promotions, banner advertising and direct mail advertising. Unique identifiers, such as IDs and passwords, are collected to validate the user’s identity, and as account numbers in our record system.

COMMENTS AND SUGGESTIONS

All comments, suggestions, ideas, designs and graphics made on the Site at any time by any user of the Site will be regarded as non-proprietary and will become the exclusive property of Guru Fantasy Reports Inc. (unless the rights to such matters are specifically reserved in writing by the user or guest at the time of submission).

SECURITY

Guru Fantasy Reports Inc. is committed to undertaking reasonable measures to protect the privacy, accuracy and reliability of your personal information and to protect such information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. Guru Fantasy Reports Inc. uses a variety of security measures to ensure the security of your personal information, and regularly monitors the Site for inappropriate or illegal activities by third parties. We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards (appropriate to the sensitivity of such information) designed to protect against unauthorized use, disclosure or access of the personal information we collect on the Site. However, the Internet is not a perfect service medium and data transmission over the Internet is not guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, Guru Fantasy Reports Inc. cannot warrant the security of the information, which the user provides to it or warrant that third parties will not unlawfully intercept the information. When information is provided (including credit card information) to Guru Fantasy Reports Inc. for any purpose, you do so at your own risk.

Some or all of the personal information we collect may be stored or processed on servers located outside your jurisdiction of residence, whose data protection laws may differ from the jurisdiction in which you live. As a result, this information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts or law enforcement agencies in those jurisdictions according to laws in those jurisdictions. Subject to applicable laws in such other jurisdictions, we will use reasonable efforts to ensure that appropriate protections are in place to require the data processor in that jurisdiction to maintain protections on the personal information that are equivalent to those that apply in the jurisdiction in which you live.

ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION

You may contact us with a request to access, update or delete any information we have about you. We will respond to your request in a prompt manner, however, before we are able to provide you with any information, correct any inaccuracies or delete any information, we may ask you to verify your identity.

COOKIES

Guru Fantasy Reports Inc. collects some information and data from the Site through the use of cookies. Cookies are information files that a web site can use to ease the access to and use of a web site. Cookies are stored on the hard drive of the individual’s computer. Cookies do not give Guru Fantasy Reports Inc. access to an individual’s personal computer or personal data that is stored therein. Cookies cannot be used to retrieve data from your personal computer or read cookies created by other sites. A cookie file can contain information such as a username the Site uses to track the pages you have visited. Additionally, once you have entered in your username and password during a session, we save that information so you don’t have to re-enter it repeatedly during that session. Users will NOT be able to use all the features of the Site, unless their personal computer accepts cookies.

CHILDREN AND PRIVACY

We encourage parents and guardians to spend time with their children online and to be fully familiar with the sites visited by their children. At various places on the Site, we may ask users for their age. By using the Site, you agree to respond truthfully and accurately about your age. Children under the age of majority in their respective province or territory are expressly prohibited from accessing any content on the Site or from submitting or posting any personal information on the Site.

MESSAGE BOARDS, CHAT ROOMS, BLOGS AND OTHER USER FORUMS

Please remember that information posted to message boards, chat rooms, blogs and other users becomes public information. Use caution when posting. Individuals should be especially careful not to provide any personally identifiable information when participating in any area of the Site where postings might become public. Please see our Terms of Use for the standards of behaviour that must be followed when using these portions of the Site.

QUESTIONS AND PERSONAL OPTIONS

If you have any questions or comments about the Guru Fantasy Reports Inc. Privacy Policy and other related state of affairs, please feel free to contact us at [support@fantasyguruelite.com](mailto:support@fantasyguruelite.com). If you need to change, update or delete information previously provided, you can edit your Guru Fantasy Reports Inc. registered information at anytime by accessing and editing your user profile.
